http://som.utdallas.edu/som/privacy-policy/

Programs
Undergraduate
BS AccountingBS Business AdministrationBS FinanceBS Global BusinessBS Healthcare ManagementBS Human Resource ManagementBS Information Technology and SystemsBS MarketingBS Supply Chain ManagementVisit JSOMBIZ 101 - School VisitsComet ClosetDavidson Management Honors ProgramFast Track ProgramsFuture UndergraduatesJindal OutREACH - Community ServiceSTEM ProgramsStudy Abroad ProgramsStudent OrganizationsUndergraduate Marketable SkillsUTDsolv
MS
MS AccountingMS Business AnalyticsOnline MS Business AnalyticsMS Energy ManagementMS FinanceMS Financial Technology and AnalyticsMS Healthcare Leadership and ManagementMS Healthcare Leadership and Management (for professionals)MS Healthcare Leadership and Management (for physicians)MS Information Technology & ManagementOnline MS Information Technology & Management
MS Innovation & EntrepreneurshipMS International Management StudiesMS Management ScienceOnline MS Management Science
MS MarketingOnline MS MarketingMS Supply Chain ManagementOnline MS Supply Chain ManagementMS Systems Engineering and ManagementOnline Master's Courses
MS/MBA (Engineering)
Double Degree - MS/MS
Double Degree - MS/MBA
Career ManagementGMAT & GRE Prep CoursesMS EventsSTEM ProgramsStudent OrganizationsStudy Abroad ProgramsMS Leadership Organizational Development (Executive Coaching)EMBA with emphasis in Product Lifecycle & Supply Chain ManagementSystems Engineering and ManagementMS Marketable Skills
MBA
Full-Time MBAProfessional MBA Evening CohortProfessional MBA FlexProfessional MBA OnlineDouble Degree - MS/MBAMBA ConcentrationsGMAT & GRE Prep CoursesMBA Career ManagementMBA EventsStudent OrganizationsMBA Marketable SkillsOnline MBA CoursesExecutive MBAGlobal Leadership MBA (online)EMBA with emphasis in Healthcare Leadership and Management (for physicians)EMBA with emphasis in Product Lifecycle & Supply Chain ManagementEMBA with emphasis in Project Management
PhD
International Management StudiesManagement ScienceAdmissionsFundingPhD Student ProfilesPhd Marketable Skills
Executive Education
Executive MBAGlobal Leadership MBA (online)EMBA with emphasis in Healthcare Leadership and Management (for physicians)Product Lifecycle & Supply Chain ManagementEMBA with emphasis in Project ManagementCorporate ProgramsMS Leadership Organizational Development (Executive Coaching)Systems Engineering and ManagementExecutive & Professional Coaching EMBA with emphasis in Product Lifecycle/Supply Chain Management EMBA with emphasis in Project ManagementAcademic Certificates (Executive)Professional Certificates (Executive)
Centers & Institutes
Center and Laboratory for Behavioral Operations and Economics (LBOE)Center for the Analysis of Property Rights and Innovation (CAPRI)Center for Finance Strategy and Innovation(CFSI)Center for Global Business (CGB)Center for Healthcare Leadership and Management (CHLM)Center for Information Technology and Management (CITM)Center for Intelligent Supply Networks (C4iSN)Center for Professional SalesInternal Auditing Excellence (IAEP)International Accounting Development: Oil and GasInternational Center for Decision and Risk Analysis (ICDRIA)The Leadership CenterMorris Hite CenterHerbert D. Weitzman Institute for Real EstateInstitute for Excellence in Corporate Governance (IECG)The Institute for Innovation & Entrepreneurship (IIE)
Resources
Blackboard (eLearning) ServicesBusiness Communication CenterBusiness CompetitionsComet ClosetDean's CouncilStudy Abroad ProgramsLiving Learning CommunityMcDermott Library SatelliteMcKinney ProgramsStudent OrganizationsStudent ResearchTechnology and Facilities ServicesWeb ServicesJSOM LabsAccounting Tutoring LabExcel LabFinance Trading LabExcel LabUndergraduate ScholarshipsGraduate ScholarshipsGraduate AssistantshipsAcademic CalendarCourse CatalogGMAT & GRE Prep CoursesMath Refresher Course
Application Process
Undergraduate AdmissionsMS AdmissionsMBA AdmissionsPhD AdmissionsExecutive Education AdmissionsCertificate ProgramsTuition Plans
Resources
FAQAboutAdvisingCareersScholarshipsFaculty & ResearchStaffAlumniMake a GiftSocial Media
Blog
Skip to Main Content
Advising
Careers
Scholarships
Faculty & Research
Staff
Alumni
Application Process
Undergraduate ProgramsBS AccountingBS Business AdministrationBS FinanceBS Global BusinessBS Healthcare ManagementBS Human Resource ManagementBS Information Technology and SystemsBS MarketingBS Supply Chain ManagementUndergraduate ResourcesVisit JSOMBIZ 101 - School VisitsComet ClosetDavidson Management Honors ProgramFast Track ProgramsFuture UndergraduatesJindal OutREACH - Community ServiceMarketable SkillsOnline Undergraduate CoursesSTEM ProgramsStudent OrganizationsStudy Abroad ProgramsUTDsolv
MS ProgramsMS AccountingMS Business AnalyticsMS Energy ManagementMS FinanceMS Financial Technology and AnalyticsMS Healthcare Leadership and ManagementMS Information Technology & ManagementMS Innovation & EntrepreneurshipMS International Management StudiesMS Management ScienceMS MarketingMS Supply Chain ManagementMS Systems Engineering and Management
MS/MBA (Engineering)Double Degree - MS/MSDouble Degree - MS/MBAOnline MS ProgramsOnline MS Programs OverviewMS Business Analytics OnlineMS Information Technology & Management OnlineMS Management Science OnlineMS Marketing OnlineMS Supply Chain Management OnlineExecutive MS Programs
MS Leadership Organizational Development (Executive Coaching)
MS Healthcare Leadership and Management (for professionals)MS Healthcare Leadership and Management (for physicians)MS Supply Chain Management Executive EducationSystems Engineering and ManagementMS ResourcesCareer ManagementMS EventsOnline Master's CoursesSTEM ProgramsStudent OrganizationsMS Marketable Skills
MBA ProgramsFull-Time MBAProfessional MBA Evening CohortProfessional MBA FlexProfessional MBA OnlineDouble Degree - MS/MBAMBA Concentrations
MBA ResourcesGMAT & GRE Prep CoursesMBA Career ManagementOnline MBA CoursesMBA EventsStudent OrganizationsMBA Marketable Skills
Executive MBA Programs
Executive MBAGlobal Leadership MBA (online)EMBA with emphasis in Healthcare Leadership and Management (for physicians)EMBA with emphasis in Healthcare Leadership and Management (for professionals)EMBA with emphasis in Product Lifecycle & Supply Chain ManagementEMBA with emphasis in Project Management
International Management StudiesManagement ScienceDegree PlanAccounting ConcentrationFinance ConcentrationInformation Systems ConcentrationMarketing ConcentrationOperations ConcentrationAdmissionsFunding
PhD Student ProfilesAccounting PhD StudentsFinance PhD StudentsInternational Management PhD StudentsInformation Systems PhD StudentsMarketing PhD StudentsOperations Management PhD StudentsPhD Marketable Skills
Executive MBA Programs
Executive MBAGlobal Leadership MBA (online)EMBA with emphasis in Healthcare Leadership and Management (for physicians)EMBA with emphasis in Healthcare Leadership and Management (for professionals)EMBA with emphasis in Product Lifecycle & Supply Chain ManagementEMBA with emphasis in Project Management
Corporate Education
Corporate Programs
Executive MS Programs
MS Leadership Organizational Development (Executive Coaching)MS Healthcare Leadership and Management (for professionals)MS Healthcare Leadership and Management (for physicians)MS Supply Chain Management Executive EducationSystems Engineering and Management
CertificatesAcademic CertificatesProfessional Certificates
CentersCenter and Laboratory for Behavioral Operations and Economics (LBOE)Center for the Analysis of Property Rights and Innovation (CAPRI)Center for Finance Strategy and Innovation (CFSI)Center for Global Business (CGB)Center for Healthcare Leadership and Management (CHLM)Center for Information Technology and Management (CITM)
Centers (cont.)
Center for Intelligent Supply Networks (C4iSN)Internal Auditing Excellence (IAEP)Center for Professional SalesInternational Accounting Development: Oil and GasInternational Center for Decision and Risk Analysis (ICDRIA)The Leadership CenterMorris Hite Center
InstitutesHerbert D. Weitzman Institute for Real EstateInstitute for Excellence in Corporate Governance (IECG)The Institute for Innovation & Entrepreneurship (IIE)
ServicesBlackboard (eLearning) ServicesBusiness Communication CenterBusiness CompetitionsComet ClosetDean's CouncilGrad Students Business CardsJindal OutREACH - Community ServiceStudy Abroad ProgramsLiving Learning CommunityMcDermott Library SatelliteMcKinney Programs
Services (cont.)
Student OrganizationsStudent ResearchTechnology and Facilities ServicesWeb Services
Labs
JSOM LabsAccounting Tutoring LabExcel LabFinance Trading Lab
Scholarships/Assistantships
Undergraduate ScholarshipsGraduate ScholarshipsGraduate Assistantships
UTD Resources
Academic CalendarCourse Catalog
Prep Courses
GMAT & GRE Prep CourseMath Refresher Course
Undergraduate AdmissionsMS AdmissionsMBA AdmissionsPhD AdmissionsExecutive Education AdmissionsCertificate ProgramsTuition Plans
Jindal
>
Naveen Jindal School of Management Privacy Policy
Naveen Jindal School of Management Privacy Policy
Naveen Jindal School of Management Privacy Policy
In respect of your privacy, the UT Dallas Naveen Jindal School of Management does not collect personal information about visitors. In particular, we do not use “cookies” to collect personal information.
Personal information that you provide via email or other online means will be used only to serve your needs. Such uses might include simple responses to questions or something as complex as considering you for enrollment. The service may involve redirecting your inquiry, information or comment to another person or department better suited to meet your needs.
We may use server logs to collect information concerning your Internet connection and general information about your visit to our website. This information may be used to analyze trends, to create summary statistics to help in determining technical design specifications and to identify system performance or problem areas.
If you have questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your use of this website, please contact the Webmaster.
Last Updated: June 2, 2020
